font_type:
Mona
font_size:
24
draw_off_x:
24
draw_off_y:
24
draw_step_add_y:
2



ITEM_レア_カリバーン:
［Caliburn: Noble Phantasm］
The Golden Sword of Promised Victory.
Also handy for picking the class committee or
assigning cleaning duties!


ITEM_レア_凛のペンダント:
［Tohsaka's pendant: accessory］
A memento. Unfortunately, it's already empty.


ITEM_レア_偽臣の書:
［Book of False Attendant: other］
Hand-made by Sakura, a useful item that is sure to bring Rider along.


ITEM_レア_天の杯:
［Holy Grail: accessory］
Einzbern treasure.
Equip your Illya to make her into Perfect Illya!


ITEM_レア_ジャプニカ暗殺帖:
［Japunika Assassination Note: other］
Illya's revenge notebook. Includes the plan to assassinate Shirou.


ITEM_レア_セイバーのぬいぐるみ:
［Saber's stuffed toy: accessory］
The stuffed toy lion she got from Shirou. Saber's favorite.


ITEM_レア_セイバーの茶碗:
［Saber's rice bowl: tableware］
Saber's bowl, filled with delicious white rice.
Another Holy Grail, in a sense.


ITEM_レア_ライダーの眼鏡:
［Rider's glasses: accessory］
A seal for Rider's Mystic Eyes of Petrification.
Should she take them off carelessly, a large-scale disaster will occur.


ITEM_レア_キャスターのコイン:
［Caster's coin: Noble Phantasm］
A highly valuable coin. Cannot be used in a vending machine, sadly.


ITEM_レア_キャスターの指輪:
［Caster's ring: accessory］
A gift she received from her beloved Kuzuki-sensei... not.
Just a regular ring.


ITEM_レア_エクスカリバー:
［Excalibur...?: Noble Phantasm］
Dropped by Gilgamesh, a sword that greatly resembles Excalibur.
Good for throwing?


ITEM_レア_金ぴか耳飾り:
［Golden earrings: accessory］
Majestic-looking earrings, probably made of solid gold.
These would sell for a lot.


ITEM_レア_ランサーの釣竿:
［Lancer's fishing rod: tool］
The Rod of Impaling Barbed Death,
reverses the nature of cause and effect.
Get fish first, angle later.


ITEM_レア_アーチャーのスリッパ:
［Archer's slippers: accessory］
An amazing product that lets you lounge around the
house without taking your boots off.
Shoes strictly prohibited.


ITEM_レア_アーチャーのお玉:
［Archer's ladle: tableware］
A strongman's ladle, projected by Archer.
Unlimited Cooking Works.


ITEM_レア_タイガーストラップ:
［Tiger strap: accessory］
Just having the decorative Tiger strap increases your luck.
Be careful, the tail breaks off easily.


ITEM_レア_メイド服:
［Maid uniform: accessory］
A nurse-like white uniform.
Has the fragrance of a noble family.


ITEM_レア_掛け軸:
［Hanging scroll: other］
A hanging scroll that used to decorate the Emiya dojo.
Are there different types, or did the writing just change...?


ITEM_レア_ビーフ２０００:
［Beef 2000: food］
Some lovely canned catfood.
....Er, tasty-looking catfood.


ITEM_レア_泰山のレンゲ:
［A spoon from Taizan: tableware］
Property of Koushuuensaikan Taizan.
Used to enjoy delicious mapo tofu.


