
--------------------------------------------------------------------------------
	About this file - the basics
	
	- Pre-Ryuudou Lake lines are between #begin1 and #end
	- Lines just before the Illya battle are between #begin2 and #end
	- Blank line starts a new page
	- #fontsize sets font size in pixels
	- #fontface sets font name
	- #left sets the left margin in pixels
	- #top sets the top margin in pixels
	- #say plays the voice file

--------------------------------------------------------------------------------


#begin1

#fontsize 26
#fontface Mona
#left 30
#top 30
#say FIR_TIG_0000
Welcome, chosen ones!!

#say FIR_TIG_0010
The time has come to challenge the winter castle, but
watch your every step!


#say FIR_TIG_0020
Many great trials await you! The image of your loved ones
and family in your heart, I want you to overcome them all!


#say FIR_TIG_0030
"Three more days and we're free" - no!!
Shake it off, become one with your Master and Servant,
and be a legend!


#say FIR_TIG_0040
Are you even listening?
That devil, still an apprentice, daring to challenge me,
her teacher...


#say FIR_TIG_0050
Could it be she wants a heroine's seat for herself!?
Put simply, you are also in trouble!
The peaceful times have finally come to an end!


#say FIR_TIG_0060
Yes, you, the nonchalant ones, lacking any tension
whatsoever! You will soon understand what that ankle-biter
of a Holy Grail feels!


#say FIR_TIG_0070
...Remember the time you feared for your own place?
Yep, like that...


#say FIR_TIG_0080
But now, I am Taiga! Stern to bow, a heartless warship
with no mercy aboard! Engraved in my heart, the spirit
of my mind!


#say FIR_TIG_0090
Soldiers, I wish you luck in your valiant struggles!
Flare up, one-shot lighters!!


#say FIR_TIG_0100
Oh, and make sure you read the tutorial. Relying on pure
chance will not keep you alive. However, as you keep
progressing, remember that luck is still the final
unknown.

#end









#begin2

#fontsize 26
#fontface Mona
#left 30
#top 30
#say FIR_TIG_0110
Officer Fuji's radio is Mexican!


#say FIR_TIG_0120
.......


#say FIR_TIG_0130
....It's not. I lied.


#say FIR_TIG_0140
...Ahem.


#say FIR_TIG_0150
You've done admirably in surviving up to now,
chosen ones!


#say FIR_TIG_0160
The detested castle is right before you! Throw down the
challenge to the silver-haired mistress, but take care!


#say FIR_TIG_0170
And with that, my fellow troops, I wish to give you a few
heartfelt words of encouragement. Listen up!

#fontsize 60
#left 130
#top 60
#say FIR_TIG_0180
Comrades!!


#fontsize 26
#left 30
#top 30
#say FIR_TIG_0190
Seeing blood being washed with blood, this display of
violence brings tears to your teacher's... No, your
commander's eyes!


#say FIR_TIG_0200
Why can you not get along!?
Why must you stop your fellow soldiers!?
And by the way, wasn't the mushroom big enough!?


#say FIR_TIG_0210
At any rate, you will not be able to defeat that girl
with such unsightly behavior. That's right, you will
have to attack her together at once!
Well, that's what I was told, anyway.


#say FIR_TIG_0220
Come now, let us unite and forget the cold lands of
treachery, once and for all! Fallen comrades, tears of
the final struggle, unforeseen conclusion, a commercial
break at the right spot...


#say FIR_TIG_0230
The adventure, the ending where everyone's chasing
something flying along the enbankment, all that scenery
in your mind...


#say FIR_TIG_0240
Go forth and be brave, oh chosen ones!!
Do not hold back and shine like the sun!!

#end