意味	キーワード	発言１		発言２		発言３	
親決め選択前に	before_oya	....Are you ready?\nLet's begin the tutorial.	Yep.	Please pick one card\nfrom the table in the middle.	I will.	The player that picks an earlier\nmonth becomes the dealer.	
親決め選択後に	after_oya	%oya% the dealer.\nThe cards will now be dealt.					
ラウンド開始後、選択状態に入る前に	roundstart	The game is set up.%tefuda%%bafuda%\nIt is now %oya2% turn.					
場に同月3枚	samemon3	If there are 3 cards of the same month on the table,\nthey'll be put together.	Pile up?	Whoever puts another card of the same month\non the table, picks up all 3.	So you get 4 cards total.		
プレイヤーターン-手札	plte	Please pick one card from your hand.\n%tefuda%Then pick one from the table.%bafuda%	Okay. But which one?	The ones you can pick\nwill have a blue border around them.	You're right!	Point at one with your mouse,\nand all the cards of that month will start blinking.	
プレイヤーターン-手札(合札なし)	plte_none	There are no cards on the table that match\nthe months in your hand, sadly.\nYou still have to pick one card and\nplace it on the table, however.	Aww~. Which one, I wonder?	For the time being,\na Dreg card would be a safe choice.	The least valuable one?	Once you grasp the relationship between\ncards and yaku, I'm sure you will become\nquite adept at choosing cards that need\nto be left behind, as well.	
プレイヤーターン-手札(合札有り)	plte1	Have you noticed?\nThere is a matching month on the table.	Yeah.				
プレイヤーターン-手札(合札2枚)	plte2	There are two cards that have a matching month\non the table. Please pick one.%bafuda%	Okay.				
プレイヤーターン-手札(合札を取った)	plte3	These cards are now yours.\nPlease take them.	Got it.				
プレイヤーターン-手札(合札なし)	plte4	There is no matching month,\nand the card remains on the table.	Aw, can't take it.....				
プレイヤーターン-手札(手札に合札2枚)	plte5	There are 2 cards in your hand that match the\nmonth of the card you picked. Pick one of them.%tefuda%	This one.				
プレイヤーターン-山札	plyama	One more card will now be drawn from the deck.%yamafuda%\nThis card will always be placed on the table first.					
プレイヤーターン-山札(場に合札がある)	plyama1	One of cards on the table has the same month\nas the card that was just drawn.					
プレイヤーターン-山札(場に合札が2枚ある)	plyama2	Two of the cards on the table have the same month\nas the card that was just drawn. Please pick one.	This one.				
プレイヤーターン-山札(選んだら)	plyama3	These cards are now yours.	Okay.				
プレイヤーターン-山札(合札なし)	plyama4	Looks like there are no cards with a matching month.\nTherefore, this card will stay on the table.	Can't take it.....				
プレイヤーターン-終了	plend	Is it all right?\nYour turn is about to end.	Yep.	If you happen to forget the types of cards,\nor the yaku they can form, please feel free\nto click on these buttons to view the reference list.%list%	Roger.		
いずれかがテンパイになったら	tenpai	%player% need just one more card to form a yaku.	The yaku icon came on.	If you right-click on the yaku icon underneath the cards,\nyou can see which card is needed.\nGo ahead and try it.	Thanks.		
CPUに役ができたら	cpuyaku	I now have a yaku formed among the cards I have.	Eh?				
CPUに役ができたら(こいこい)	cpukoikoi	However, I am not quite satisfied with it.\nI believe I can form another one.\nTherefore, I declare "Koi-Koi" and continue the game.	Ohh.....				
CPUに役ができたら(勝負)	cpuagari	Having formed a yaku, I can now declare "game".	Can you?				
プレイヤーに役ができたら	plyaku	Once you form a yaku,\nyou can choose whether to call "Koi-Koi" or "Game".	Ummm......	If you feel you can still form another,\nor if you are not satisfied with the score,\nyou can declare "Koi-Koi" and continue playing.	Hm.	Declare "Game" if you would rather settle\nwith what you have.	Hm, hm.
対戦終了(勝負あり)	kachimake	Once "Game" is declared, the total value of all\nformed yaku is subtracted from the opponent's score.	Ohh.	The player that won will\nbecome the dealer in the next round.			
対戦終了(引き分け)	hikiwake	If both players run out of cards before forming a yaku,\nor the player that called "Koi-Koi" was unable\nto form another one, the game ends in a draw.	Too bad.	Other player becomes the dealer,\nbut neither of them lose points.			
おわり	finish	The tutorial is only one round,\nbut the actual game will continue until the score is\nreduced to zero.%cpupoint%	I see.	It may be a little difficult to understand at first,\nbut please try to have fun while memorizing\nthe cards and yakus.	Okay.	---Good luck.	
